seo-website-designer.com 2015-12-03

# Privacy Policy for Web Site Advantage

.

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Web Site Advantage collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site. 

##  Personal identification information

When you fill in our contact form you will be providing personal information. We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. 

##  Web browser cookies

When you visit our site, short text files called cookies are downloaded to your computer. These cookies are used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis and marketing. 

This website uses Google Analytics for Display Advertisers to collect visitor data and analyse traffic on our site. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our website and marketing. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/or notify you before they are placed. 

##  Third party website advertising

Web Site Advantage may use the available information from the cookies to advertise to you on other websites that are part of the Google Display Network. This is called remarketing. 

You can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers and opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=ACi0TCiRDcnrXrdffABE6Nifr9QppTwHkj_NTB8gd0FaMd9YV_wg5YIp3OvYIp-y-pdTWNhIhLjQXh6TyIek2jcL233J8XokduMKuR1N-zHOJP2Ls6zIAM_wKkwTu-xTmML-Aucg-KSrCOB6oLAL11n-sPX9rEefGBMsmC7iVBTJsDKZmWkr3jnzCeVGR-wzwiV8cGO96yfR&hl=en) . There is also a [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) . 

##  Changes to this privacy policy

Web Site Advantage has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

##  Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

##  Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

Phone: (08) 7200 1664  
Web Site Advantage  
9/24 Wakefield St,  
Kent Town,   
South Australia, 5067 

This document was last updated on April 21, 2014.
